So again, that doesn't make much sense maybe,
but that's just again, to make it a bit more exciting,
and to make these two tipping functions
different for each of the persons.
Okay?
So, I want you to implement the same
functionality as before, but this time of course,
using Mark's tipping rules.
Then create a function, and I don't mean a method.
So, like an outside function to calculate
the average of a given array of tips.
And here I have to give you another hint,
because up until this point,
we never did anything like this.
Okay and so I give you a hint here to calculate the average.
And that is that you should loop over the array,
and in each iteration, store the current sum
in a variable which starts from zero.
Then after you have the sum of the array,
then you'll simply divide it by
the number of elements in it.
Okay? So that's the formula for calculating averages.
So if that's a bit too difficult for you,
then you can just stop maybe after point five.
Okay?
But I would like you to try out,
to calculate the average, alright?
So that's here on number seven,
so you use the function that you
created in number six to actually
calculate the average for both families.
And then you'll log to the console
which family paid the highest tips on average.
Alright?
So, again, this one is a bit tricky maybe,
so you can, no problem, take an hour or even more
to try to accomplish this, alright?
I think it's really important for your
learning process to go through
something like this, a bit more difficult even,
so that you really have to try,
instead of it being super easy.
Because then you don't really learn anything, okay?
So take an hour or something like that to
really go through this and really try
to solve these problems.
Alright? You don't need to be fast.
Then if there are some parts that
you cannot figure out, again, no problem,
you can just check out my solution in the next video.